{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Bird \u0026 Bat Control Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40354/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40354,"taskName":"Pest Control - Birds and Bats","taskDescription":"Control or Relocate Birds or Bats","xmTaskDescriptor":"Bird \u0026 Bat Control Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4917,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Pest Birds animal electronic exterminators","textMessagingName":"Pest Control Bird","rolloverLongDesc":"Removal of nests, birds flying indoors, attic \u0026 chimney infestations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Pest controller who handles birds or bats.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Control or Relocate Birds or Bats.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Bat \u0026 Bird Control or Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":58,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Birds \u0026 Bats Control","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pest Control - Birds and Bats","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pest Control Project","urlName":"Pest-Control-Birds-and-Bats","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Bat \u0026 Bird Control Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Cost of Removal","searchKeywords":"Pest,Birds,animal,electronic,exterminators,exterminator,exterminate,removal,Bats,Control","emcCategoryOid":-12057,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":648,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376525018pwspr013F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40354/":{"taskOID":40354,"originalTaskOID":40354,"setID":648,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":501447,"questionDisplayText":"Bird or Bat","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a bird or bat problem?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a bird or bat problem?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bird","answerDisplayText":"Bird","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bat","answerDisplayText":"Bat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4392,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the specific bird or bat control problem? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3100,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House siding damage","answerDisplayText":"House siding damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Noise","answerDisplayText":"Noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1046,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bird waste","answerDisplayText":"Bird waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":710,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aggresive birds","answerDisplayText":"Aggresive birds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6251,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Taking fruit from trees","answerDisplayText":"Taking fruit from trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5695,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the problem? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2138,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Eaves","answerDisplayText":"Eaves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2282,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Exhaust vents","answerDisplayText":"Exhaust vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6640,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Utility lines","answerDisplayText":"Utility lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":501447,"questionDisplayText":"Bird or Bat","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a bird or bat problem?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a bird or bat problem?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bird","answerDisplayText":"Bird","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bat","answerDisplayText":"Bat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bird","answerDisplayText":"Bird","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bat","answerDisplayText":"Bat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4392,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the specific bird or bat control problem? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3100,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House siding damage","answerDisplayText":"House siding damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Noise","answerDisplayText":"Noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1046,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bird waste","answerDisplayText":"Bird waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":710,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aggresive birds","answerDisplayText":"Aggresive birds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6251,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Taking fruit from trees","answerDisplayText":"Taking fruit from trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3100,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House siding damage","answerDisplayText":"House siding damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Noise","answerDisplayText":"Noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1046,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bird waste","answerDisplayText":"Bird waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":710,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Aggresive birds","answerDisplayText":"Aggresive birds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6251,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Taking fruit from trees","answerDisplayText":"Taking fruit from trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5695,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the problem? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2138,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Eaves","answerDisplayText":"Eaves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2282,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Exhaust vents","answerDisplayText":"Exhaust vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6640,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Utility lines","answerDisplayText":"Utility lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2138,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Eaves","answerDisplayText":"Eaves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2282,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Exhaust vents","answerDisplayText":"Exhaust vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6640,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Utility lines","answerDisplayText":"Utility lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}